zootool.com 2019-11-15

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how I, Bastian Allgeier, collect, use, and share information in connection with your use of this website ([https://bastianallgeier.com](https://bastianallgeier.com/)).

Bastian Allgeier  
Böhmer Weg 22  
69151 Neckargemünd  
Germany

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact me at [mail@bastianallgeier.com](mailto:mail@bastianallgeier.com).

## Your Data Protection Rights

You always have the right to access all personal information I hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact me: [mail@bastianallgeier.com](mailto:mail@bastianallgeier.com).

You may always file a complaint with your national data protection authorities regarding the use of your data. But please tell me first so I have a chance to sort things out.

## Collected Information

Generally, I don’t collect any personal information about you on this website. This website does not store any local storage information such as cookies that could identify a single, unique user. I also don't use any form of analytics tool to track visitors and page impressions.

My hosting provider [DomainFactory](https://domainfactory.com/) stores server logs, including the IP address, user agent, timestamp and status code. Those logs are kept for three days.

## Secure Data Transfer

This website transmits all data using HTTPS, encrypting all data between the browser and the server. Your network provider may still be able to see that you are loading files from bastianallgeier.com, but not their content.

## Changes to this policy

I may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to my practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

–

Last update: 17.05.2019
